[
	{
		"question": "What tv show did Britney appear in as a child?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Degrassi",
			"2": "The All New Mickey Mouse Club",
			"3": "Sam & Cat",
			"4": "Victorious"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "two"
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Britney's middle name?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Jean",
			"2": "Simpson",
			"3": "Ashley",
			"4": "Jamie"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "one"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which artist does NOT have a collaboration with Britney?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Rihanna",
			"2": "Ariana Grande",
			"3": "Will.i.am",
			"4": "Tinashe"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "two"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many Grammy nominations does Britney have?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Eight",
			"2": "Thirteen",
			"3": "Five",
			"4": "One"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "one"
	},
	{
		"question": "Which tv show has Britney NOT appeared in?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Glee",
			"2": "How I Met Your Mother",
			"3": "Gossip Girl",
			"4": "Jane the Virgin"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "three"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many Grammys does britney have?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Eight",
			"2": "Four",
			"3": "Two",
			"4": "One"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "four"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many Siblings does Britney has?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "None",
			"2": "Three",
			"3": "One",
			"4": "Two"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "four"
	},
	{
		"question": "How many perfumes does Britney have?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "24",
			"2": "10",
			"3": "30",
			"4": "18"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "one"
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was Britney born?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "Tennessee",
			"2": "Louisiana",
			"3": "Mississippi",
			"4": "Florida"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "three"
	},
	{
		"question":
			"When did Britney receive a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?",
		"answers": {
			"1": "2013",
			"2": "2003",
			"3": "2000",
			"4": "2014"
		},
		"correctAnswer": "two"
	}
]
